Welcome to the Udacity C++ nanodegree program.
欢迎使用 Udacity C++ 纳米级程序
C++ is such an exciting and important language
C++ 是如此激动人心的重要语言
for everything from self-driving cars to robotics,
从自动驾驶汽车到机器人
to the internet of things,
在网络上
and we are so excited to share this language with you.
我们很高兴能和你分享这个语言
Throughout this nanodegree program,
在整个纳米级方案中
you'll learn about C++ from expert instructors who will take you from
您将从专家指导员中了解有关 C++ 的信息
the foundations of the C++ programming language
C++ 编程语言的基础
all the way through to advanced in expert topics.
都是通过专家来讨论的
One of the most exciting things about
最令人兴奋的一件事
this program is that you'll hear from Bjarne Stroustrup,
你会听到贝雅妮 - 斯特劳斯楚普的节目
the creator of C++,
C ++的创建者
who will tell you why different features of the language were designed the way they
谁会告诉你语言的不同特点
are and how to best use them to create the most effective and efficient programs.
以及如何最有效地利用它们来创建最有效和高效的程序
At Udacity, we believe in a learn-by-doing approach,
在不透明度的情况下 我们相信一个以学为本的方法
which means that in order to become a C++ engineer,
这意味着为了成为 C++ 工程师
you're going to need to write a lot of C++ code,
你需要写很多 C++ 代码
and we're going to help you do that.
我们会帮你的
By the end of this program,
在节目结束前
you'll have a job ready project portfolio full of
你就会有一个完整的项目组合
all the different C++ applications that you've built as part of this nanodegree program.
所有您所构建的不同 C++ 应用程序作为此纳米级程序的一部分
Are you ready to learn C++? Let's get started.
你准备好学 C++吗 ? 我们开始吧